{"test_questions": [[{"question": "When referring to instruction words, a mnemonic is:", "opta": "a short abbreviation for the operand address", "optb": "a short abbreviation for the operation to be performed", "optc": "a short abbreviation for the data word stored at the operand address", "optd": "shorthand for machine language", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the difference between mnemonic codes and machine codes?", "opta": "There is no difference.", "optb": "Machine codes are in binary, mnemonic codes are in shorthand English.", "optc": "Machine codes are in shorthand English, mnemonic codes are in binary.", "optd": "Machine codes are in shorthand English, mnemonic codes are a high-level language.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which bus is bidirectional?", "opta": "data bus", "optb": "control bus", "optc": "address bus", "optd": "multiplexed bus", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The software used to drive microprocessor-based systems is called:", "opta": "assembly language programs", "optb": "firmware", "optc": "BASIC interpreter instructions", "optd": "flowchart instructions", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A microprocessor unit, a memory unit, and an input/output unit form a:", "opta": "CPU", "optb": "compiler", "optc": "microcomputer", "optd": "ALU", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many buses are connected as part of the 8085 microprocessor?", "opta": "2", "optb": "3", "optc": "5", "optd": "8", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not a computer bus?", "opta": "data bus", "optb": "timer bus", "optc": "control bus", "optd": "address bus", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The technique of assigning a memory address to each I/O device in the SAM system is called:", "opta": "wired I/O", "optb": "I/O mapping", "optc": "dedicated I/O", "optd": "memory-mapped I/O", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many bits are used in the data bus?", "opta": "7", "optb": "8", "optc": "9", "optd": "16", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A port can be:", "opta": "strictly for input", "optb": "strictly for output", "optc": "bidirectional", "optd": "all the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not a basic element within the microprocessor?", "opta": "microcontroller", "optb": "arithmetic-logic unit (ALU)", "optc": "temporary register", "optd": "accumulator", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many bits are used in the address bus?", "opta": "7", "optb": "8", "optc": "9", "optd": "16", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Exceptions to the 8085 microprocessor normal operation are called:", "opta": "jump instructions", "optb": "decoding", "optc": "interrupts", "optd": "jump instructions or interrupts", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}